<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Jailbreak Scratch!</title>
        <link>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/</link>
        <description>Jailbreak Scratch!</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 17:12:20 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>Map Update 4: Cells added but bars and stairs are yet to be</title>
    <link>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/posts/2021/04/map4/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 17:12:20 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/posts/2021/04/map4/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[We are so close to finishing the main building! Soon we can move onto other maps neccessary for the game! This time, I have added the cells. At the minute, it isn&rsquo;t obvious, but soon, they will be added. Stairs are also yet to be added and what looks like to be a cell on the corner is actually a police gear up station.
Of course this needs gear, but, hey!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Map Update 3: Meeting Area &amp; Path to cells</title>
    <link>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/posts/2021/04/map3/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 17:45:47 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/posts/2021/04/map3/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[I&rsquo;m back with another map update! Today, I made the start of the meeting area. Obviously it needs chairs! Then I started the path to the cells. This is where criminals will start again when they get arrested! There will eventually be a second floor, which will be prettey cool.
That&rsquo;s all for today, until next time!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Map Progress #2</title>
    <link>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/posts/2021/04/map2/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Apr 2021 18:27:36 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/posts/2021/04/map2/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Horray! Another map update! This time, we are looking at what will eventually will be our main building. At the minute it&rsquo;s just a walkway into the cafeteria and there are benches to sit on.
The divide in the cafeteria is going to be where the food is served and it will be staff only behind it. There is also a door, which will be permantly there, since this is where you enter and exit!]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Map Progress #1</title>
    <link>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/posts/2021/03/map1/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 15 Mar 2021 19:09:44 &#43;0000</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://jailbreak-scratch.github.io/posts/2021/03/map1/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Welcome to the first map progress! Before I go into what this includes, remember you can always go to the github repo with the assests
In this update, I have added a court with a fence (fence incomplete) and a main building with a (to-be) clickable door. The background (currently) is only grass, but I will have sand and stone as I make the map.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
